<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<!--
   New Perspectives on HTML, CSS, and XML
   Tutorial 12
   Review Assignments

   List of maps sold by Map Finds For You
   Author:   
   Date:      

   Filename:         products.xml
-->

<products>
   <product>
      <name pid="HM1002P" category="historical">North America 1849</name>
      <versionDate surveyDate="1849">1968</versionDate>     
      <desc>This historical map of North America includes part of the West India Islands. 
      Old style colors are used to outline boundaries of the United States. 30 x 38 inches. 
      </desc>
      <price media="electronic">$38.00</price>
   </product>
   <product>
      <name pid="HM3042P" category="historical">Lewis and Clark: A Legacy of Science</name>
      <versionDate>2003</versionDate>
      <desc>This Lewis and Clark poster commemorating the bicentennial of this incredible 
      journey of discovery features two maps in parallel view: above is a beautiful reproduction 
      of the 1814 Lewis and Clark map; also included is the same geographic area depicted with 
      current remote sensing technology in a colorful image of the American landscape. 42 x 44.5 inches.
      </desc>
      <isbn>978-0-607-99721-7</isbn>
      <price format="flat" media="paper">$5.50</price>
   </product>
   <product>
      <name pid="SM012P" category="state">United States: Wisconsin</name>
      <versionDate>1968</versionDate>
      <desc>This state map of Wisconsin outlines borders of the state and its counties.  Some
      topography is included.  46 x 45 inches.
      </desc>
      <isbn>978-0-607-59264-1</isbn>
      <price format="flat" media="paper">$1.00</price>
   </product>
   <product>
      <name pid="PL24L" category="parks">Canyonlands National Park</name>
      <versionDate></versionDate>
      <desc>National park map of Canyonlands National Park, which is the the largest national 
      park in Utah.  Some shaded relief; contours included. 45 x 60 inches.
      </desc>
      <isbn>978-0-607-84777-2</isbn>
      <price format="flat" media="paper">$12.00</price>
   </product>
   <product>
      <name pid="HM240P" category="historical">Antietam: Historical Map of the Battlefield of Antietam</name>
      <versionDate>1904</versionDate>
      <desc>The National Geospatial-Intelligence Agency (NGA) created these attractive and 
      informative posters to celebrate the legacy of battlefield cartography, photo interpretation, 
      and imagery analysis. This is one of a series of 14 maps based on surveys of the Antietam 
      Battlefield showing military positions during the course of the battle. These maps were 
      created in response to a congressional mandate to document significant Civil War 
      battlefields. The purpose was to gain a greater understanding of the movement of troop, 
      artillery, and cavalry units as they maneuvered to win an advantage. 36 x 24 inches.
      </desc>
      <price format="flat" media="paper">$12.00</price>
   </product>
   <product>
      <name pid="HM250P" category="historical">Normandy Air Campaign</name>
      <versionDate>1945</versionDate>
      <desc>The National Geospatial-Intelligence Agency (NGA) created these attractive and 
      informative posters to celebrate the legacy of battlefield cartography, photo interpretation, 
      and imagery analysis. This map shows fighter plane patrol routes in assault areas. The map 
      legend identifies flight routes across the English Channel, positions of naval ships, 
      assault beaches, and more. Foreground image is of P47s flying in patrol formation during 
      the invasion. 36.5 x 24.5 inches.
      </desc>
      <price format="flat" media="paper">$10.00</price>
   </product>
</products>